<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Setup on Pcluster Manager Docs</title><link>https://pcluster.cloud/01-getting-started.html</link><description>Recent content in Setup on Pcluster Manager Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 09:05:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pcluster.cloud/01-getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>a. Access AWS</title><link>https://pcluster.cloud/01-getting-started/01-aws-console-login.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 10:46:30 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://pcluster.cloud/01-getting-started/01-aws-console-login.html</guid><description>Depending on your workshop, you may access the AWS Management Console through direct sign-in (here) or as directed by your trainer. To sign in, enter your AWS Account ID or alias, IAM user name, and password that was provided to you for this lab.
After you sign in, take a few minutes to explore the navigation components of the AWS Management Console.
A search bar allows you to quickly locate services based on text.</description></item><item><title>b. Deploy Pcluster Manager</title><link>https://pcluster.cloud/01-getting-started/02-pcmanager-install.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pcluster.cloud/01-getting-started/02-pcmanager-install.html</guid><description>The AWS ParallelCluster API has been released with the version 3 of AWS ParallelCluster. It enables you to to manage clusters though an API hosted on AWS and build workflows to manage your cluster lifecycle with Python.
Pcluster Manager is a web UI that built upon the AWS ParallelCluster CLI that you can use to manage your compute clusters. It&amp;rsquo;ll take about 20 minutes to deploy both stacks. You will initiate the deployment now to have it ready by the time you need it.</description></item><item><title>c. Connect to Pcluster Manager</title><link>https://pcluster.cloud/01-getting-started/03-pcmanager-connect.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pcluster.cloud/01-getting-started/03-pcmanager-connect.html</guid><description>During deployment you received an email titled [PclusterManager] Welcome to Pcluster Manager, please verify your account.. Click on the link to login with the temporary code provided. Enter the credentials using the email you used when deploying the stack and the temporary password from the email above. You will be asked to provide a new password. Enter a new password to complete signup. Congrats! You are ready to create your HPC cluster in AWS.</description></item><item><title>d. Summary</title><link>https://pcluster.cloud/01-getting-started/04-summary.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pcluster.cloud/01-getting-started/04-summary.html</guid><description>In this part of the lab you deployed the AWS ParallelCluster API and Pcluster Manager. You should see a screen that looks like:</description></item></channel></rss>