<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tutorials on Pcluster Manager Docs</title><link>https://pcluster.cloud/02-tutorials.html</link><description>Recent content in Tutorials on Pcluster Manager Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 09:05:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pcluster.cloud/02-tutorials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>a. Setup SMS for MFA 📱</title><link>https://pcluster.cloud/02-tutorials/01-setup-sms.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 10:46:30 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://pcluster.cloud/02-tutorials/01-setup-sms.html</guid><description>To enable Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA) with Pcluster Manager there&amp;rsquo;s two setup steps that need to be completed.
Setup an Origination number Add a sandbox number 1. Setup an Origination Number Navigate to Pinpoint Phone Numbers Console &amp;gt; Click Request Phone Number
Fill out the following options:
Option Description Country [Your Country] Number Type Toll Free Capabilities SMS Default Message Type Transactional Click Next &amp;gt; Request
2. Add a sandbox number Next navigate to the SNS SMS Console &amp;gt; Click Add a phone number</description></item><item><title>b. Slurm Accounting 🪄</title><link>https://pcluster.cloud/02-tutorials/02-slurm-accounting.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pcluster.cloud/02-tutorials/02-slurm-accounting.html</guid><description>In this tutorial we will work through setting up Slurm Accounting. This enables many features within slurm, including job resource tracking and providing a necessary building block to slurm federation.
Step 1 - Setup External Accounting Database The first requirement is to setup an external database that Slurm can use to store the accounting data.
Use the following CloudFormation Quick-Create link to create the database in your AWS account. Note that if you would like to create the database in a different region, change the value of the region parameter in the URL to the region of your choice and reload the page.</description></item><item><title>c. Memory Scheduling 💾</title><link>https://pcluster.cloud/02-tutorials/03-memory-scheduling.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pcluster.cloud/02-tutorials/03-memory-scheduling.html</guid><description>Slurm supports memory based scheduling via a --mem or --mem-per-cpu flag provided at job submission time. This allows scheduling of jobs with high memory requirements, allowing users to guarantee a set amount of memory per-job or per-process.
For example users can run:
sbatch --mem-per-cpu=64G -n 8 ... To get 8 vcpus and 64 gigs of memory.
In order to add in memory information, we have a managed post-install script that can be setup with Pcluster Manager.</description></item><item><title>d. Cost Tracking 💰</title><link>https://pcluster.cloud/02-tutorials/04-cost-tracking.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pcluster.cloud/02-tutorials/04-cost-tracking.html</guid><description>Cost Tracking is essential to every single HPC workload, it&amp;rsquo;s important to be able to track costs per-user, per-project, per-slurm-partition and track these costs overtime.
There&amp;rsquo;s two different ways to setup cost tracking, each with their own tradeoffs:
To see historical spend on a per-job basis, setup Slurm Accounting 🪄. This will allow you to query for job runtimes, who submitted what jobs, how many instances and duration of the job.</description></item><item><title>d. Cloud9 ☁️</title><link>https://pcluster.cloud/02-tutorials/05-cloud9.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pcluster.cloud/02-tutorials/05-cloud9.html</guid><description>Cloud9 is a web-based code editor, terminal and file-browser. You can connect to the cluster via Cloud9 and advantage of the following convenient features:
Terminal Drag &amp;amp; Drop file upload Code editor Setup To setup the connection, we need to run a script to install the Cloud9 packages on the HeadNode.
From the Pcluster Manager GUI create a new cluster. Select the Wizard option: On the HeadNode configuration tab Expand Advanced Options &amp;gt; turn on Multi-Script Runner &amp;gt; select Cloud9 On the final screen review and make sure your config looks similar to the following.</description></item></channel></rss>